Guide to the Burney Family Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Burney Family Collection, Series I
  - BURNEY, JAMES, 1750-1821
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1818 Feb 25 (Box 8, Folder 573)
    - Letter to Sir Philip Stephens, 1783 Apr 17 (Box 8, Folder 574)
    - Letter to [Sharon] Turner, [post 1802?] (Box 8, Folder 575)
    - Letter to unnamed recipient, 1820 Nov 9 (Box 8, Folder 576)
    - Signature on a [British Museum] Call slip, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 577)
    - Notes of books, 1811 Apr 26 (Box 8, Folder 578)
  - BURNEY, MARTIN CHARLES, 1788-1852
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1839 Sep-Dec (Box 8, Folder 579)
  - BURNEY, RICHARD, 1790-1845
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1821 Oct 9 (Box 8, Folder 580)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1822 Feb 1 (Box 8, Folder 581)
  - BURNEY, SARAH HARRIET, 1772-1844
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., [1795]-1812 (Box 8, Folder 582)
    - Letter to Richard Burney, 1813 Oct 7 (Box 8, Folder 583)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1814 Jan 26 (Box 8, Folder 584)
    - Letter to Rosette (Rose) Burney, 1815 Oct 4 (Box 8, Folder 585)
    - Letters to Johann Christian Hüttner, 1808-09 (Box 8, Folder 586)
    - Letter to [an admirer of her book], [ca. 1807-14] (Box 8, Folder 587)
    - Letter to a sister, 1794 Oct 19 (Box 8, Folder 588)
    - Letters to Henry Colburn, 1820-1821 (Box 8, Folder 589)
  - CADELL AND DAVIES, PUBLISHERS
    - Letter to [Charles Burney, D.D.], [1802] (Box 8, Folder 590)
  - CAMBRIDGE, GEORGE OWEN, 1756-1841
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1803 Mar 29 (Box 8, Folder 591)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1803 Apr 5 (Box 8, Folder 592)
  - CAMBRIDGE, RICHARD OWEN, 1717-1802
    - Letter to Frances Burney d'Arblay, [ca. 1784-85] (Box 8, Folder 593)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D>, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 594)
  - CAMPBELL, THOMAS, 1777-1844
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1821 Dec 17 (Box 8, Folder 595)
  - CAMPION, GEORGE, 1846-1926
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1903 Mar 21 (Box 8, Folder 596)
  - CANNING, GEORGE, 1770-1827
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus. D., 1808 Jul 23 (Box 8, Folder 597)
  - CANTERBURY, CHARLES MANNERS-SUTTON, 1780-1864
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1830 Apr 18 (Box 8, Folder 598)
  - CARDIGAN, ROBERT BUSHNELL, 5TH EARL OF, 1725-1811
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus. D., 1807-[09] (Box 8, Folder 599)
  - CARDWELL, EDWARD, 1787-1861
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [1811 Oct 7] (Box 8, Folder 600)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1818-25 (Box 8, Folder 601)
  - CAROLINE AMELIA ELIZABETH, QUEEN CONSORT OF
    [George IV, 1768-1821]
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., [1810-18] (Box 8, Folder 602)
    - Formal invitation to dinner for Charles Burney, D.D., n.d. (Box 8, Folder 603)
  - CARTER, MRS. MARY
    - Letter to Frances Burney d'Arblay, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 604)
  - CHALMERS, ALEXANDER, 1759-1834
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1784-[94] (Box 8, Folder 605)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1819-33, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 606)
  - CHAMIER, ANTHONY, 1725-1780
    - Letters to Charles Burney Mus.D., 1776-1780 (Box 8, Folder 607)
  - CHANTREY, SIR FRANCIS LEGATT, 1781-1841
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1819-34 (Box 8, Folder 608)
  - CHAPMAN, J. M., REV.
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1868 Nov 12 (Box 8, Folder 609)
  - CHARLEY, SIR WILLIAM THOMAS, 1833-1904
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1885 Feb 12 (Box 8, Folder 610)
  - CHARLOTTE AUGUSTA, PRINCESS, 1796-1817
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1806 Sep 3 (Box 8, Folder 611)
  - CHAULNES, LOUIS-MARIES-JOSEPH-ROMAIN D'ALBERT
    [d'Ailly, duc de, 1741-1792]
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus. D., [ca. 1780-90?] (Box 8, Folder 612)
  - CHURTON, EDWARD TOWNSON, BISHOP OF NASSAU
    [1841-1912]
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1886-88 (Box 8, Folder 613)
  - CLAGGET, CHARLES, 1740-1800
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus. D., 1791 Aug 10 (Box 8, Folder 614)
  - CLARK, H. M.
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1846 Dec 4 (Box 8, Folder 615)
  - CLAUGHTON, THOMAS LEGH, BISHOP OF ST. ALBAN'S
    [1802-1892]
    - Letters to Charles Burney IV, [ca. 1867-90] (Box 8, Folder 616)
  - CLEMENTS, JACOB, 1821-
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1898 [May 28] (Box 8, Folder 617)
  - COLCHESTER, ENG. (ARCHDEACONRY)
    - Petition to Charles Parr Burney, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 618)
  - COLENSO, JOHN WILLIAM, 1814-1883
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1854 Dec 11 (Box 9, Folder 619)
  - COLERIDGE, JOHN DUKE COLERIDGE, BARON, 1820-1894
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1876 [Feb 19] (Box 9, Folder 620)
  - COLERIDGE, SIR JOHN TAYLOR, 1790-1876
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1835-47 (Box 9, Folder 621)
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1869 Dec 8 (Box 9, Folder 622)
  - COLMAN, GEORGE, 1732-1794
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [post 1797] (Box 9, Folder 623)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., [ca. 1783]-88 (Box 9, Folder 624)
  - CONYBEARE, WILLIAM DANIEL, 1787-1857
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, [post 1821]-48 (Box 9, Folder 625)
  - COOKE, JOHN, 1738-1823
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 626)
  - COPELAND, WILLIAM JOHN, 1804-1885
    - Letters to Charles Burney IV, 1871-74 (Box 9, Folder 627)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1842 Apr 2 (Box 9, Folder 628)
  - COPLESTON, EDWARD, BISHOP OF LLANDAFF, 1776-1849
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1810 Nov 26 (Box 9, Folder 629)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1815 Jan 10 (Box 9, Folder 630)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1815 Feb 1 (Box 9, Folder 631)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1827 Nov 11 (Box 9, Folder 632)
  - CORDINER, CHARLES, 1746?-1794
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1781 Feb-Jul (Box 9, Folder 633)
  - COTMAN, JOHN SELL, 1782-1842
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1834 Jan 17 (Box 9, Folder 634)
  - COURTENAY, JOHN, 1741-1816
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1810 Jul 22 (Box 9, Folder 635)
  - COX, HENRY, CA. 1777-1844
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1832 Mar 16 (Box 9, Folder 636)
  - COX, RICHARD, 1718-1803
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1791-98 (Box 9, Folder 637)
  - CREWE, FRANCES ANNE (GREVILLE), 1748-1818
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., [1803], 1804 (Box 9, Folder 638)
    - Letters to Frances Burney d'Arblay, 1814, 1781 (Box 9, Folder 639)
  - CRISP, SAMUEL, 1707-1783
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1770, 1776 (Box 9, Folder 640)
  - CROMBIE, ALEXANDER, 1762-1840
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, [post 1818], 1830 (Box 9, Folder 641)
  - CROSS, CHARLES
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1790 Dec 9 (Box 9, Folder 642)
  - CROTCH, WILLIAM, 1775-1847
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1790, 1791 (Box 9, Folder 643)
  - DALLAWAY, JAMES, 1763-1834
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1822, 1824 (Box 9, Folder 644)
  - DAMPIER, THOMAS, BISHOP OF ELY, 1748-1812
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1802-08 (Box 9, Folder 645)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1809-11 (Box 9, Folder 646)
  - DANCE, GEORGE, 1741-1825
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1799 Jan 25 (Box 9, Folder 647)
  - DANIELL, THOMAS, 1749-1840
    - Letter to [Charles Burney, D.D.], 1805 Nov 21 (Box 9, Folder 648)
  - DAVIDSON, RANDALL THOMAS, ARCHBISHOP OF
    [Canterbury, 1848-1930]
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1881 Nov 13 (Box 9, Folder 649)
  - DAVY, MARTIN, 1763-1839
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1804 Mar-Sep (Box 9, Folder 650)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, [1806] Oct 12 (Box 9, Folder 651)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1809 Jun-Jul (Box 9, Folder 652)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1818 Mar 3 (Box 9, Folder 653)
  - DE GRANGEBLANCHE, ----
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1766 Aug 27 (Box 9, Folder 654)
  - DENISON, GEORGE ANTHONY, 1805-1896
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1883 Jul 14 (Box 9, Folder 655)
  - DEVISME, LOUIS, 1720-1776
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1772 (Box 9, Folder 656)
  - DIBDIN, THOMAS FROGNALL, 1776-1847
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1828-35 (Box 9, Folder 657)
  - DICKENSON, MARY (HAMILTON), 1756-1816
    - Letter to Frances Burney d'Arblay, 1784 Jul 26 (Box 9, Folder 658)
  - DIDEROT, DENIS, 1713-1784
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1771-77 (Box 9, Folder 659)
  - DILLON, EDWARD
    - Letter to Charles Burney V, 1907 Mar 24 (Box 9, Folder 660)
  - DIXON, JOHN
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1788-1810 (Box 9, Folder 661)
  - DOBREE, PETER PAUL, 1782-1825
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1802-04 (Box 9, Folder 662)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1805-07 (Box 9, Folder 663)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1808-12 (Box 9, Folder 664)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1816-17 (Box 9, Folder 665)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, [1824?] Oct 24 (Box 9, Folder 666)
  - DOBSON, AUSTIN, 1840-1921
    - Letters to Charles Burney V, 1902-04 (Box 9, Folder 667)
  - DOUGLAS, JOHN, BISHOP OF SALISBURY, 1721-1807
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1790 Apr 28 (Box 9, Folder 668)
  - DRURY, HENRY
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1816 Nov 6 (Box 9, Folder 669)
  - DUNBAR, JAMES, D. 1798
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1779-89 (Box 9, Folder 670)
  - DUNCAN, LADY MARY (TUFTON), D. 1806
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [pre-1784] (Box 9, Folder 671)
  - DYER, GEORGE, 1755-1841
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., [1814?]-15 (Box 9, Folder 672)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, [1819 Apr 6] (Box 9, Folder 673)
  - EDEN, GEORGE RODNEY, BISHOP OF WAKEFIELD
    [1853-1940]
    - Letters to Charles Burney IV, 1896-97 (Box 9, Folder 674)
  - EDGEWORTH, RICHARD LOVELL, 1744-1817
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1797-99 (Box 9, Folder 675)
  - EDWARDS, JAMES, 1757-1816
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1810 Jul 10 (Box 9, Folder 676)
  - EDWARDS, THOMAS WILLIAM CHARLES
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1833 Jul (Box 9, Folder 677)
  - ELLIOTT, CHARLES JOHN, BISHOP OF
    [Gloucester, 1785-1864]
    - Letter to [Charles Parr Burney], 1858 Dec 21 (Box 9, Folder 678)
  - ELLIS, SIR HENRY, 1777-1864
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1818 Sep 3 (Box 9, Folder 679)
  - ELMSLEY, PETER, 1773-1825
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1807-13 (Box 9, Folder 680)
  - ENGLEFIELD, SIR HENRY CHARLES, 1752-1822
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1809 Jul 14 (Box 9, Folder 681)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [post 1815 Aug] (Box 9, Folder 682)
  - ERSKIN, THOMAS ERSKINE, BARON, 1750-1823
    - Letter to [Charles Parr Burney], 1808 Aug 13 (Box 9, Folder 683)
  - FARNBOROUGH, CHARLES LONG, 1ST BARON, 1761-1838
    - Letter to [Charles Burney, Mus.D.], 1809 Oct 16 (Box 9, Folder 684)
  - FARRAR, FREDERIC WILLIAM, 1831-1903
    - Letters to Charles Burney IV, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 685)
  - FEILDING, WILLIAM ROBERT FEILDING
    [styled viscount, 1760-1799]
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1792 Jun 25 (Box 9, Folder 686)
  - FIELDING, ANTHONY VANDYKE COPLEY
    [1787-1855]
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1829, 1852 (Box 9, Folder 687)
  - FINCH, ROBERT, 1783-1830
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1816-27 (Box 9, Folder 688)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1827-28 (Box 9, Folder 689)
  - FISHER, DOROTHEA SCRIVENOR
    - Letter to Frances Burney d'Arblay, 1813 Feb 19 (Box 9, Folder 690)
  - FITZGERALD, KEANE, D. 1782
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1767 May 9 (Box 9, Folder 691)
  - FORDYCE, JAMES, 1720-1796
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1787-92 (Box 9, Folder 692)
  - FORSHALL, JOSIAH, 1795-63
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1840 Dec 15 (Box 9, Folder 693)
  - FORSTER, CHARLES, REV., CA. 1787-1871
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1869 Feb 20 (Box 9, Folder 693a)
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1869 Jul 26 (Box 9, Folder 693b)
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1869 Jul 27 (Box 9, Folder 693c)
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1869 Nov 12 (Box 9, Folder 693)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1860 Mar 31 (Box 9, Folder 693e)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1861 Jul 7 (Box 9, Folder 693)
  - FOSCOLO, UGO, 1778-1827
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1816 Sep 13 (Box 9, Folder 694)
  - FOSTER, J. J.
    - Letter to [Charles Burney V], 1906 Nov 25 (Box 9, Folder 695)
  - FRANCIS, DR. CLEMENT, D. 1792
    - Letter to Mrs. [Esther] Burney, 1786 Feb 28 (Box 9, Folder 696)
  - FRITH, WILLIAM POWELL, 1819-1909
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1878 May 4 (Box 9, Folder 697)
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, [1890] Aug 17 (Box 9, Folder 698)
  - FRYER, C. G. LYNN
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, [1840] Jul 18 (Box 9, Folder 699)
  - FUSELI, HENRY, 1741-1825
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1802-08 (Box 9, Folder 700)
  - GAISFORD, THOMAS, 1799-1855
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [1803]-10 (Box 9, Folder 701)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1808-16 (Box 9, Folder 702)
  - GELL, JOHN HENRY, CA. 1771-1856
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1817 Feb 22 (Box 9, Folder 703)
  - GERARD, GILBERT, 1760-1815
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., ca. 1780 (Box 9, Folder 704)
  - GERARD, ALEXANDER, 1792-1839
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1780 Apr 23 (Box 10, Folder 705)
  - GERARD, GILBERT, 1760-1815
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1780-81 (Box 10, Folder 706)
  - GIARDINI, FELICE, 1716-1796
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [ca. 1774]-88 (Box 10, Folder 707)
  - GIBBS, HENRY H.
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1896 Jan 8 (Box 10, Folder 708)
  - GILLIES, JOHN, 1747-1836
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [1780] (Box 10, Folder 709)
  - GIMINGHAM, WILLIAM, CA. 1773-1838
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1824 Sep 27 (Box 10, Folder 710)
  - GLASSE, GEORGE HENRY, 1761-1809
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1789 Aug-Oct (Box 10, Folder 711)
  - GOBLET, [LEWIS]
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [1823] (Box 10, Folder 712)
  - GODDARD, WILLIAM STANLEY, 1757-1845
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1829 Mar 16 (Box 10, Folder 713)
  - GOLDING, RICHARD, 1785-1865
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, [post 1818?] Jul 3 (Box 10, Folder 714)
  - GOLDRING, DOUGLAS, 1887-1960
    - Letters to Mr. Burney, 1949 Apr (Box 10, Folder 715)
  - GOODALL, JOSEPH, 1760-1840
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1788-1810 (Box 10, Folder 716)
  - GORDON, ABERCROMBIE
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1780-81 (Box 10, Folder 717)
  - GORDON, THOMAS
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1780 Sep 15 (Box 10, Folder 718)
  - GOULBURN, EDWARD MEYRICK, 1818-1897
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1869 Jun 5 (Box 10, Folder 719)
  - GOTT, JOHN, BISHOP OF TRURO, 1830-1906
    - Letters to Charles Burney IV, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 720)
  - GRAHAM, JOHN, BISHOP OF CHESTER, 1794-1865
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1846-48 (Box 10, Folder 721)
  - GRAVES, RICHARD, 1715-1804
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus. D., n.d. (Box 10, Folder 722)
  - GRAY, ELSPET
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1810 Jul 13 (Box 10, Folder 723)
  - GRAY, SIR JAMES, 2ND BART., CA. 1708-1773
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1772 Jun 28 (Box 10, Folder 724)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1780-81, 1784 (Box 10, Folder 725)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1783-[ca. 1787] (Box 10, Folder 726)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1790, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 727)
  - GREGORY, ROBERT, 1819-1911
    - Letters to Charles Burney IV, 1891-94 (Box 10, Folder 728)
  - GRENVILLE, THOMAS, 1755-1846
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1813 Dec 29 (Box 10, Folder 729)
  - GREVILLE, CHARLES CAVENDISH FULKE, 1794-1865
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, [post 1811]-[34] (Box 10, Folder 730)
  - GREVILLE, LADY CHARLOTTE (BENTINCK), D. 1862
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [1812] Sep 14 (Box 10, Folder 731)
  - GREVILLE, FRANCES (MACARTNEY), D. 1789
    - Letter to Esther Sleepe Burney, 1760 Oct 2 (Box 10, Folder 732)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus. D., 1767 Oct-Nov (Box 10, Folder 733)
  - GREVILLE, RICHARD FULKE
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1764-66, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 734)
  - GRIFFITHS, GEORGE EDWARD, 1768-1829
    - Letters to Burney family members, 1784-1811, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 734a-c)
  - GRIFFITHS, RALPH, 1720-1803
    - Letters to Burney family members, 1784-95 (Box 10, Folder 734d-g)
  - GARRICK, DAVID, 1717-1779
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [ca. 1775-78] (Box 10, Folder 735)
  - GUI, [PIERRE]
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus. D., 1771 Apr 8 (Box 10, Folder 736)
  - GUILFORD, FRANCIS NORTH, 4TH EARL OF, 1761-1817
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1815, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 737)
  - GUILFORD, FREDERICK NORTH, 5TH EARL OF, 1766-1827
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1792 Sep 14 (Box 10, Folder 738)
  - GUILFORD, FRANCIS NORTH, 4TH EARL OF, 1761-1817
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., n.d. (Box 10, Folder 739)
  - GUILFORD, FREDERICK NORTH, 5TH EARL OF, 1766-1827
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [pre-1804] (Box 10, Folder 740)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1818 Sep-Oct (Box 10, Folder 741)
  - GUSCOTTE, WADHAM, & BRADBURY
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1899 Apr 24 (Box 10, Folder 742)
  - HALE, WILLIAM HALE, 1795-1870
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1854, 1862 (Box 10, Folder 743)
  - HALES, M., MISS
    - Letter to Mrs. Elizabeth Burney, [1796 Mar 20] (Box 10, Folder 744)
  - HALIBURTON, JAMES, 1788-1862
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1850 Aug 24 (Box 10, Folder 745)
  - HAMILTON, SIR WILLIAM, 1730-1803
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1770, 1802 (Box 10, Folder 746)
  - HARCOURT, MARY (DANBY) LOCKHART HARCOURT
    [Countess of]
    - Letters to Frances Burney d'Arblay, 1813-14 (Box 10, Folder 747)
  - HARDING, JAMES DUFFIELD, 1798-1863
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1832 Sep (Box 10, Folder 748)
  - HARRINGTON, HENRY, 1727-1816
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1773-1806 (Box 10, Folder 749)
  - HARRIS, JAMES, 1709-1780
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1772-79 (Box 10, Folder 750)
  - HARRIS, BENJAMIN, 1808-1887
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1880 Apr 6 (Box 10, Folder 751)
  - HART, ROBERT
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1887 Nov 25 (Box 10, Folder 752)
  - HART, SOLOMON ALEXANDER, 1806-1881
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1833 May 13 (Box 10, Folder 753)
  - HASSE, JOHANN ADOLPH, 1699-1783
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1773 Apr 27 (Box 10, Folder 754)
  - HASTINGS, WARREN, 1732-1818
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1799 Jan 30 (Box 10, Folder 755)
  - HAWKE, EDWARD HAWKE, 1774-1824
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1819 May 4 (Box 10, Folder 756)
  - HAWKINS, EDWARD, 1789-1882
    - Letters to Charles Burney IV, 1857, 1858 (Box 10, Folder 757)
  - HAYDN, JOSEPH
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [1791], 1804 (Box 10, Folder 758)
  - HAYES, PHILIP
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1779 Jul 7 (Box 10, Folder 759)
  - HAYMAN, ANNE, CA. 1753-
    - Letter to [Charles Parr Burney], [1818] Jan 13 (Box 10, Folder 760)
  - HEBER, REGINALD, BISHOP OF CALCUTTA, 1783-1826
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1804 May 2 (Box 10, Folder 761)
  - HEBER, RICHARD, 1773-1833
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1799-1816 (Box 10, Folder 762)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1818-23 (Box 10, Folder 763)
  - HENSLOW, CECILIA MARIA
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1804 Apr 25 (Box 10, Folder 764)
  - HERSCHEL, SIR WILLIAM, 1738-1822
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1797-99 (Box 10, Folder 765)
  - HEWLETT, JOHN, 1762-1844
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1813 Jan (Box 10, Folder 766)
  - HEY, JOHN, 1734-1815
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1790 Jul 14 (Box 10, Folder 767)
  - HIRONS, ANNE (CLARKE)
    - Letter to Rosette (Rose) Burney, 1776 May 29 (Box 10, Folder 768)
  - HIRONS, JABEZ, 1728-1812
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1809 Jul (Box 10, Folder 769)
  - HOARE, HENRY, AND COMPANY, BANKERS
    - Letter to Frances Burney d'Arblay, 1827 Apr 11 (Box 10, Folder 770)
  - HOARE, PRINCE, 1755-1834
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1812-13 (Box 10, Folder 771)
  - HOBHOUSE, SIR BENJAMIN, BART., 1757-1831
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1806-15 (Box 11, Folder 772)
  - HOBHOUSE, HENRY WILLIAM, 1791-1868
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [post 1810] Jul 16 (Box 11, Folder 773)
  - HOLBACH, PAUL HEINRICH DIETRICH, BARON D'
    [1723-1789]
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus. D., 1771 Dec 15 (Box 11, Folder 774)
  - HOLDERNESSE, ROBERT D'ARCY, 4TH EARL OF
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1776 Jan 7 (Box 11, Folder 775)
  - HOLE, SAMUEL REYNOLDS, 1819-1904
    - Letters to Charles Burney IV, 1883-1901 (Box 11, Folder 776)
  - HOLLAND, HENRY SCOTT, 1847-1918
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 777)
  - HOLLAND, JAMES, 1800-1870
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1862 Oct 9 (Box 11, Folder 778)
  - HOOD, SAMUEL, 1724-1816
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1806 Jan 6 (Box 11, Folder 779)
  - HOOD, THOMAS, 1799-1845
    - Letter to Charlotte (Francis) (Box 11, Folder 780)
      - Barrett, n.d.
  - HOOK, THEODORE EDWARD, 1788-1841
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, [1828?]-30 (Box 11, Folder 781)
  - HOPPNER, JOHN, 1758-1810
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1807 Sep (Box 11, Folder 782)
  - HOW, WILLIAM WALSHAM, BISHOP OF WAKEFIELD
    [1823-1897]
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1889 May 10 (Box 11, Folder 783)
  - HOWLEY, WILLIAM, ARCHBISHOP OF CANTERBURY
    [1766-1848]
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1818 Jan 1 (Box 11, Folder 784)
  - HUMPHRY, WILLIAM GILSON, 1815-1886
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1857 Oct-Nov (Box 11, Folder 785)
  - HUNTER, C. J.
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1813 Apr 22 (Box 11, Folder 786)
  - HUNTINGFORD, GEORGE ISAAC, BISHOP OF
    [Hereford, 1748-1832]
    - Letter to Edward Whittaker Gray, 1804 Feb 27 (Box 11, Folder 787)
  - HUTCHESON, THOMAS
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1767 Mar 21 (Box 11, Folder 788)
  - HüTTNER, JOHN CHRISTIAN, 1765-1847
    - Letter to Frances Burney d'Arblay, 1833 Jan 18 (Box 11, Folder 789)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1808 May-Jul (Box 11, Folder 790)
  - HUNTINGFORD, GEORGE ISAAC, BISHOP OF
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1785-90 (Box 11, Folder 791)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1792 (Box 11, Folder 792)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1802-03 (Box 11, Folder 793)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1804-05 (Box 11, Folder 794)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1806-07 (Box 11, Folder 795)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1808-09 (Box 11, Folder 796)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1810 (Box 11, Folder 797)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1811-16 (Box 11, Folder 798)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1817-[28] (Box 11, Folder 799)
  - HUTTON, JAMES, 1715-1795
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1773-74 (Box 11, Folder 800)
    - Letter to Clement Francis, 1789 Oct 6 (Box 11, Folder 801)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1789 Dec 20 (Box 11, Folder 802)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1790 Jun 15 (Box 11, Folder 803)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1793 Feb 21 (Box 11, Folder 804)
    - Letter to Frances Burney d'Arblay, 1793 Feb 27 (Box 11, Folder 805)
  - IDDESLEIGH, STAFFORD HENRY NORTHCOTE
    [1st Earl of, 1818-1887]
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1850 Jul 22 (Box 11, Folder 806)
  - INGLIS, JOHN, 1777-1851
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1825 Aug 9 (Box 11, Folder 807)
  - IRELAND, JOHN, 1761-1842
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1817 Feb 18 (Box 11, Folder 808)
  - IREMONGER, ELIZABETH, D. 1826
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1812-14 (Box 11, Folder 809)
  - IREMONGER, JOSHUA
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1786 Jul 7 (Box 11, Folder 810)
  - ISTED, GEORGE, 1755-1821
    - Letter to [Charles Parr Burney], 1810 Jul 5 (Box 11, Folder 811)
  - JAMARD, PRIOR OF ROCWUEFORT